Hey everyone, this is Sameer from
Dembrane.
We have an update to how your projects
are organized and we're ready to share
it with you.
Let me walk you through what's new and
what it means for you and your team.
Now, before I click into anything,
here's the big picture.
Dembrane is now organized around three
levels: organizations, workspaces, and
projects.
Now, this home screen is new as well and
it's built around search.
You can expect your recent projects to
start showing up here.
One of the other things that you'll
notice is new is the sidebar.
Up top, you've got your search
and your inbox.
Then come the organizations
inside which your workspaces sit.
And then
your language settings and your user
settings are down here.
These are kept separate from any
organization level
or workspace level settings.
An organization is your company.
Inside it are workspaces.
Now, you might have a few
internal workspaces
like these two here
and one for each client.
They stay separate.
So, a client only ever sees their own
workspace.
For example, Peter here can only see
this workspace
and never your internal work
and also never any other clients.
When you create a new workspace
you can choose who can see it. Let's
have a look.
Let's say this
workspace is for internal use.
Here, I can choose if I want everyone in
my organization to see it,
just the people I invite to see it,
or
just me.
Now, your internal workspaces run on
your organization's billing.
So, you can create any number of
workspaces you want.
A client's workspace, however, gets its
own billing.
Let's go back for now.
Now, about working together.
In any organization or workspace,
you now have the members tab,
where as an admin,
you can invite people.
Simply have to add a colleague's email,
choose a role, and send.
They will be in the same projects and
conversations as you, working right
alongside.
They'll get an email, accept, and appear
here.
Just to show you, I've switched over to
Peter's account.
Now, Peter
was invited as an external by
Facilitation BV
to this workspace. So, Peter can only
see this one workspace from Facilitation
BV as an external collaborator.
Let's talk about projects.
Inside a workspace is where your
projects live.
And if you've used TeamBrain before,
your projects will be right where you
left them.
Let's open one.
This is the new project overview page.
First, we have the QR code of the
portal,
and a quick overview of the portal
settings.
Your conversations are still all here.
Let's go over some of the other options.
Your chats now live under ask.
And you can
use Tempering Chat just like before.
While this is going on, here is the
portal editor
just like before.
And the host guide,
which you can print.
And the report.
Just to summarize, everything you
already relied on works exactly as
before.
For example, the portal editor, the
portal itself, chat, conversations,
uploading, and more.
What's new is the structure around
these.
And one more practical thing before I
wrap up. We've got scheduled maintenance
this weekend that moves everyone's
projects over to this new setup.
You won't have to do anything.
We'll create an organization and a
default workspace for you and give you
admin access.
From Monday, you'll be able to start
inviting your team.
And if something feels off or you have
an idea while you're in here, there's a
feedback button right here.
Use it. We read all of it.